I mean, I tried to stick them back on,
but before I could...
(Howard:)...you turned into a giant loaf
of pumpernickel bread.
(Howard:)What do you think that means?
(Summer(uncomfortable):)I really don't know.
(Howard:)I'll give you a little clue.
My favorite sandwich?
Salami on pumpernickel.
(Summer:)Is that so?
Did you know the word pumpernickel comes
from the German words pumper and knickel.
(Howard:)Which loosely translates to fart goblin?
(Summer:)No. I didn't.
(Penny:)Okay, I found the box. Now what?
(Sheldon:)You're holding a Japanese puzzle box,
which takes 10 precise moves to open.
Okay, first locate the
panel with the diamond pattern...
...and slide the center portion
1 millimeter to the left.
(Sheldon:)Then, on the opposite end of the box...
(Sheldon:)...slide the entire panel
down 2 millimeters.